Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, we would start discussing about wrapper classes. We will try and understand what are wrapper
在这段视频中，我们将开始讨论包装器类的问题。我们将尝试并理解什么是包装器
classes and also we'd discuss about why do we need wrapper classes.
类，同时我们也会讨论为什么我们需要包装器类。
What are wrapper classes?
什么是封装器类？
So, we know that there are a lot of primitive variable types that we have already discussed about, right.
所以，我们知道有很多原始变量类型，我们已经讨论过了，对吧。
So, boolean, byte, char, double, float,
所以，布尔型、字节型、图表型、双倍型、浮点型。
int is the one which we used frequently, long, and short.
int是我们经常使用的一种类型，还有long和short。
The thing is, in Java,
问题是，在Java中。
there are corresponding classes for each of these primitive types. So, these classes are called wrapper
这些原始类型的每一个都有相应的类。所以，这些类被称为包装器
classes, because they are like a wrapper around this value.
类，因为它们就像是这个值的一个包装。
So, if I take int, the wrapper class is Integer. All the other ones are exactly the same names, so boolean,
所以，如果我拿int来说，包装器类就是Integer。其他的都是完全一样的名字，所以是布尔型。
Boolean except for char as well. So, char is Character.
布尔类，除了char也是如此。所以，char是Character。
So, the wrapper class for char is Character, for int is Integer and all the others is just the same
所以，char的封装类是Character，int的封装类是Integer，其他的都是一样的
name with a capital alphabet starting off.
名称，并以大写字母开头。
This is how your wrapper classes are now.
这就是你的封装类现在的样子。
The question might be, okay, if I have primitive values why do I really need a wrapper class?
问题可能是，好吧，如果我有原始值，为什么我真的需要一个封装类？
Why do I need a wrapper class?
为什么我需要一个包装器类呢？
The thing about wrapper classes is, they offer you a lot of options, additional options.
关于包装器类的问题是，它们为你提供了很多选择，额外的选择。
Let's say I would want to create a boolean value from a string or I would want to create a integer value
比方说，我想从一个字符串创建一个布尔值，或者我想从一个字符串创建一个整数值。
from a string.
或者我想从一个字符串中创建一个整数值。
You can do that using wrapper classes.
你可以用包装器类来做这些。
The other things that wrapper class provides are a number of utility methods.
包装器类提供的其他东西是一些实用方法。
So, let's say, I have a float and I would want the integer value of that specific float.
所以，比方说，我有一个浮点数，我想得到这个特定浮点数的整数值。
I can use a intValue( ) method.
我可以使用一个intValue( )方法。
Let's say I want to convert a string which is in binary format. So, binary is 0 and 1s.
比方说，我想转换一个二进制格式的字符串。所以，二进制是0和1。
So, let's say, I have a string in the binary format and I would want to convert it into integer representation.
所以，比方说，我有一个二进制格式的字符串，我想把它转换为整数表示。
There are a lot of utility methods like this which are offered by the wrapper classes. And also, wrapper
有很多像这样的实用方法，是由包装器类提供的。另外，包装器
classes
类
allow you to store primitive values into a collection.
允许你将原始值存储到一个集合中。
We will talk about collections, a little later. If you want to add anything to a collection,
我们将在稍后讨论集合的问题。如果你想在一个集合中添加任何东西。
it must be an object and wrapper classes provide the objects around these primitives. Don't really worry
它必须是一个对象，而包装器类提供了围绕这些基元的对象。不要担心
if you are not able to understand these methods, we would discuss them in detail a little later.
如果你不能理解这些方法，我们将在稍后详细讨论它们。
The idea behind this video was to introduce you to the concept of wrapper classes and understand why
这段视频的目的是向你介绍包装器类的概念，并理解为什么我们需要包装器类。
do we need wrapper classes.
我们为什么需要包装器类。
We'll discuss about each of these wrapper classes and some of the important methods which are present
我们将在下一个视频中讨论每个封装类和其中的一些重要方法。
in them in the next video.
以及其中的一些重要方法，将在下一个视频中讨论。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，再见了。